[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "name": "Charizard",
    "type": "Fire",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/charizardFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/charizardBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "name": "Arcanine",
    "type": "Fire",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/arcanineFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/arcanineBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "name": "Blastoise",
    "type": "Water",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/blastoiseFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/blastoiseBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "name": "Vaporeon",
    "type": "Water",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/vaporeonFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/vaporeonBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "name": "Greninja",
    "type": "Water",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/greninjaFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/greninjaBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "name": "Jolteon",
    "type": "Electric",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/jolteonFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/jolteonBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "name": "Magnezone",
    "type": "Electric",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/magnezoneFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/magnezoneBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "name": "Electivire",
    "type": "Electric",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/electivireFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/electivireBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "name": "Lapras",
    "type": "Water",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/laprasFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/laprasBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "name": "Froslass",
    "type": "Ice",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/froslassFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/froslassBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "name": "Muk",
    "type": "Poison",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/mukFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/mukBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "name": "Serperior",
    "type": "Grass",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/serperiorFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/serperiorBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "name": "Gengar",
    "type": "Ghost",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/gengarFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/gengarBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "name": "Venusaur",
    "type": "Grass",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/venusaurFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/venusaurBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": true
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "name": "Torterra",
    "type": "Grass",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/torterraFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/torterraBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "name": "Scizor",
    "type": "Bug",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/scizorFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/scizorBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "name": "Volcarona",
    "type": "Bug",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/volcaronaFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/volcaronaBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "name": "Tyranitar",
    "type": "Rock",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/tyranitarFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/tyranitarBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "name": "Donphan",
    "type": "Rock",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/donphanFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/donphanBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "name": "Garchomp",
    "type": "Ground",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/garchompFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/garchompBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "name": "Onix",
    "type": "Ground",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/onixFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/onixBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "name": "Dragonite",
    "type": "Dragon",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/dragoniteFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/dragoniteBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "name": "Giratina",
    "type": "Dragon",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/giratinaFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/giratinaBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "name": "Infernape",
    "type": "Ghost",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/infernapeFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/infernapeBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "name": "Mimikyu",
    "type": "Ghost",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/mimikyuFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/mimikyuBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "name": "Blaziken",
    "type": "Fire",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/blazikenFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/blazikenBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "name": "Rayquaza",
    "type": "Flying",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/rayquazaFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/rayquazaBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "name": "Lucario",
    "type": "Fighting",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/lucarioFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/lucarioBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "name": "Mew",
    "type": "Psychic",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/mewFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/mewBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "name": "Sylveon",
    "type": "Fairy",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/sylveonFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/sylveonBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "name": "Gardevoir",
    "type": "Psychic",
    "image_front": "/gif/sprites/front/gardevoirFront.gif",
    "image_back": "/gif/sprites/back/gardevoirBack.gif",
    "nickname": "",
    "max_hp": 100,
    "attack": 50,
    "stamina": 50,
    "unlocked": false
  }
]